[id: ubkknzsh]
[ar:2NE1]
[ti:Can't Nobody (English Version)]
[00:00.00][00:11.51][00:44.24][00:58.76][01:14.35][01:29.00][01:43.79][01:51.05][02:06.02][02:20.68][02:35.96][03:02.65][03:21.73][03:25.34]
[00:00.52]Balmain to KTZ
[00:02.38]Many style from A to Z
[00:04.11]Jeremy Scott Givenchy
[00:05.98]Bitch you ain’t got shit on me
[00:07.72]Chrome hearts
[00:08.65]Fendi furs
[00:09.65]Dripped in shits you never heard
[00:15.11]Ridin’ down Seoul city
[00:17.04]Black on black Lamborghini
[00:18.84]Haters can’t never see me
[00:20.76]Come and get me, too slow
[00:22.55]I’m bout that paper chasing
[00:24.49]Body, fly face amazing
[00:26.17]Burn burn keeps it blazin
[00:28.03]Too hot to handle, can’t touch this
[00:29.89]You think you with it with it
[00:31.88]But you can’t hit it hit it
[00:33.80]U know I got it got it
[00:35.54]Cuz I’m so bout it bout it
[00:37.47]I let them hoes know
[00:39.08]I run this show show
[00:40.95]We get it poppin
[00:42.12]And we stick you for your dough dough
[00:44.42][00:51.19][01:51.24][01:58.02]Cuz I’m so bad bad
[00:45.73][00:53.06][01:52.61][01:59.88]But I’m so good good
[00:47.53][00:54.79][01:54.36][02:01.68]Yeah I’m so bad bad
[00:49.40][00:56.72][01:56.16][02:03.54]And I’m so hood hood
[00:59.76][01:12.24][02:06.21][02:18.88]Can’t nobody hold us down
[01:03.42][02:09.74]Nothing’s gonna take us down
[01:06.65][02:12.98]And you think you can stop it
[01:08.70][02:15.03]But we just can’t stop it tonight
[01:14.54][01:21.80][02:20.87][02:28.14]Can’t nobody can’t nobody hold us down
[01:18.07][02:24.52]We gon’ keep it goin’ bout to run this town
[01:25.34][02:31.73]Cuz we keep rockin’ we keep rockin’
[01:29.32]So watch out when we come for you
[01:31.13]Cuz playtime it’s done for you
[01:32.80]It’s my time and it’s my time
[01:34.60]I’m pound for pound, best to ever come around
[01:36.71]Be patient it’s never been done
[01:38.44]Asians we rise with the sun
[01:40.31]Invasion, no mercy
[01:41.92]Takeover, we thirsty
[01:44.22]Every show we shut it down
[01:45.90]Blow your speakers with this sound
[01:47.89]Build you up then break you down
[01:49.63]We comin to your town
[02:47.63][03:02.85]Let’s rock!
[02:49.06][02:56.38][03:03.85][03:11.11]Just take it to the top
[02:50.92][02:58.31][03:05.65][03:12.92]Ain’t never gonna stop
[02:52.72][03:07.51]Now all I wanna do is
[02:54.83][03:09.50]Make you rock
[03:00.12][03:14.81]Now make em say NA-NA-NA-NA
[03:17.76][03:19.62]NA-NA-NA-NA
[03:22.92]credit: romanization.wordpress.com
