[id: sbnkvasq]
[ar:Michael Heart]
[ti:We Will Not Go Down]
[al:Song for Gaza]
[00:00.00][02:07.78][03:02.81]
[00:04.92]A blinding flash of white light
[00:08.08]Lit up the sky over Gaza tonight
[00:14.04]People running for cover
[00:17.41]Not knowing whether they’re dead or alive

[00:24.18]They came with their tanks and their planes
[00:28.52]With ravaging fiery flames
[00:33.12]And nothing remains
[00:35.92]Just a voice rising up in the smoky haze

[00:40.46][00:57.72][01:43.18][02:01.19][02:24.27][02:41.98][02:50.99]We will not go down
[00:44.86][01:47.35][02:27.94][02:46.33]In the night, without a fight
[00:49.46][01:52.31][02:33.03]You can burn up our mosques and our homes and our schools
[00:54.12][01:57.03][02:37.81]But our spirit will never die
[01:02.13][02:05.55][02:57.45]In Gaza tonight

[01:08.03]Women and children alike
[01:11.07]Murdered and massacred night after night
[01:16.53]While the so-called leaders of countries afar
[01:21.19]Debated on who’s wrong or right

[01:25.98]But their powerless words were in vain
[01:31.19]And the bombs fell down like acid rain
[01:35.66]But through the tears and the blood and the pain
[01:39.02]You can still hear that voice through the smoky haze



