[id: oqsciksv]
[ar:Justin Bieber]
[ti:Eenie Meenie]
[al:My World 2.0]
[Encoding:utf-8]
[00:00.68]Eenie meenie miney mo
[00:02.43][02:16.59][02:24.65]Catch a bad chick by her toe
[00:04.25][02:18.78][02:26.91]If she holla' (if, if, if she holla) let her go
[00:08.18]Shes indecisive
[00:10.37]She can't decide
[00:12.37]She keeps on lookin'
[00:14.50]From left to right
[00:16.37]Girl, c'mon get closer
[00:18.12]Look in my eyes
[00:19.94]Searchin' is so wrong
[00:21.81]I'm Mr. Right
[00:23.67][01:25.90]You seem like the type
[00:25.23][01:28.72]To love em' and leave em'
[00:27.35]And disappear right after this song.
[00:30.10][01:34.03]So give me the night
[00:32.73][01:36.59]To show you, hold you
[00:35.17][01:39.28]Don't leave me out here dancin' alone
[00:38.17]You can't make up your mind, mind, mind, mind, mind
[00:42.17][01:45.85][02:49.28]Please don't waste my time, time, time, time, time
[00:46.29]I'm not tryin' to rewind, wind, wind, wind, wind
[00:50.17][01:53.71][02:57.28]I wish our hearts could come together as one
[00:54.04][01:57.65]Cause shorty is a eenie meenie miney mo lova'
[00:58.10][01:02.41][01:06.41][02:01.65][02:05.81][02:09.60][02:33.47][02:37.47][02:41.34][03:01.09][03:05.09][03:09.15][03:12.97]Shorty is a eenie meenie miney mo lova'
[01:11.60]Let me show you what your missin'
[01:14.04]Paradise
[01:15.66]With me you're winning girl
[01:17.84]You don't have to roll the dice
[01:19.40]Tell me what you're really here for
[01:21.78]Them other guys?
[01:23.53]I can see right through ya'
[01:31.15]And disappear right after the song.
[01:41.85][02:46.03]Can't make up your mind, mind, mind, mind, mind
[01:49.84][02:53.09]Not tryin' to rewind, wind, wind, wind, wind
[02:14.78][02:22.59]Eenie meenie miney moe
[02:30.66]Eenie meenie miney mo lova'
[03:17.90]

