[id: hcbuuksc]
[ar:YUSUF ISLAM]
[ti:I LOOK I SEE]
[al:I LOOK, I SEE]
[00:01.71][00:02.87][00:31.23][00:59.05][01:19.12][01:43.97][01:48.20][02:13.39][02:19.86]
[00:02.12]I Look I See
[00:03.92][02:16.31]I look, I look, I look, I see
[00:07.89]I see a world of beauty
[00:11.38]I touch, I touch, I touch, I feel
[00:15.80]I feel a world around so real
[00:19.87][01:36.52]And everything I do
[00:23.83][01:40.43]I dedicate to You
[00:27.81][01:44.16]Cause You made me
[00:29.74][01:46.42]I am for You
[00:31.86][00:59.69]I listen, listen, listen, I hear
[00:35.46]I hear the words of God so clear
[00:39.44]I read, I read, I read, I know
[00:43.61]It helps my knowledge grow
[00:47.76][02:04.32]And everything we do
[00:51.72][02:08.10]We dedicate to You
[00:55.45][02:12.21]Cause You made us
[00:57.75][02:14.41]We are for You
[01:04.28][02:20.85][02:37.31]He sent the Prophet to show us the way
[01:07.76][02:24.34][02:41.17]He made Religion perfect that Day
[01:11.96][02:28.57][02:45.02]Peace be upon him, upon him we pray
[01:15.88][02:32.42][02:49.36]Salatullah, wa salamu â€˜alyhi
[01:20.96]I sleep I sleep, I sleep, I dream
[01:24.50]I dream I am in a garden green
[01:28.11]I wish, I wish, I wish I pray
[01:32.64]I pray to be here everyday
[01:48.51]I work, I work, I work, I strive
[01:52.06]To make something of my life
[01:56.15]I seek, I seek, I seek, I find
[02:00.30]I find another hill to climb
