[id: blpssusq]
[al:Isonmic]
[offset:500]
[ar:Enrique Iglesias]
[ti:Miss You]
[Encoding:windows-1251]
[00:00.00]Enrique Iglesias
[00:02.00][00:09.00][00:13.00]
[00:03.00]Insomniac
[00:05.00]Track : Miss You
[00:06.00]Yeah
[00:11.00]By :RD

[00:15.66]Tonight I feel so cold and lonely
[00:20.33]And baby you’re so far away
[00:25.92]The space between us keeps on growing
[00:30.03]How I wish that you could hear me when I say

[00:35.20][00:40.92][01:30.21][01:35.29][02:17.26][02:22.91]no no no no no no no
[00:38.87][02:20.99]wish you hear me saying
[00:44.28][00:46.80][00:54.40][00:56.84][01:39.13][01:41.49][01:49.05][01:51.51][02:26.58][02:28.53][02:36.12][02:38.60][02:46.32][02:48.80][02:55.97][02:58.38]oh I miss you
[00:50.17][01:44.88][02:31.96][02:51.73]oh baby since you walked away
[01:00.07][01:54.68][02:41.78][03:01.56][03:06.60][03:11.08][03:16.07]I miss you more and more each day

[01:10.35]now tell me do you think about me
[01:15.48]Coz I think about you all the time yeah
[01:20.53]A million miles just stand between us
[01:24.94]but I don't wanna stop until your mine

[01:34.00]wish you can hear me saying

[01:59.91][02:09.74][02:12.54]Dale mamacita que la vide tiene ritmo

[02:04.76]Dale mamacita que la videtiene ritmo



[03:17.07]~~Ravi Dubey~~

