[id: kvzlkasu]
[ar:Ungu]
[ti:I Need You]
[al:1000 Kisah satu Hati]
[by:Adventino_Do3wY]
[00:00.92][00:51.27][01:47.57][02:38.44]Oh baby don’t you know how much i love you
[00:03.78][00:54.07][01:50.73][02:41.55]Oh baby don’t you know how much i miss you
[00:06.90][00:57.25][01:09.87][01:53.86][02:06.97][02:44.66]Oh baby don’t you know it’s true
[00:14.13][03:29.28]By: Adventino_Do3wY
[00:25.70]I - L - O - V - E - U, i love you
[00:38.20]I - M - I - S - S - U, i miss you


[01:03.59][02:00.80][02:51.07]Oh baby don’t you know how much i need you
[01:06.70][02:03.79][02:54.18]Oh baby don’t you know how much i want you
[01:17.22]
[01:22.25]I - N - E - E - D - U, i need you
[01:34.75]I - W - A - N - T - U, i want you


[02:16.43]By : Adventino_Do3wY

[02:57.34]Oh baby baby i want you
[03:05.50]Baby baby how much i love you
[03:18.40]Baby baby how much i need you
